Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/miapray-835809a4 (LinkedIn) vimeo.com/443237736 (Portfolio)

Top Skills
Photoshop
ZBrush

CG modeling

Mia Pray

3D Artist @ Meta

Los Angeles, California, United States

Summary

Experienced 3D Modeler and Texture Artist with a demonstrated history of working in the Animation industry. Skilled in Zbrush, Maya, Adobe Photoshop, and Substance Painter. Strong arts and design professional graduated from Ringling College of Art and Design.

Experience

Meta

3D Artist @ Meta

March 2022 - Present (1 year 2 months)

Los Angeles, California, United States

Psyop

3D Artist

September 2020 - February 2022 (1 year 6 months)

California, United States

Modeled and textured for Clash of Clans, Apex Legends and other unannounced projects.

Communicated efficiently with a lead to complete assets and address notes.

Hasbro

1 year 7 months

Freelance Digital Sculptor

July 2019 - July 2020 (1 year 1 month)

3D Sculptor/Designer

January 2019 - June 2019 (6 months)

Bubank, California

Communicated with designers to sculpt using multiple computer software

Consistently prepared files for 3D printing

Proficiently articulated various types of figures/toys

Collaborated with other sculptors to critique and create various types of products from girl or boy brands such as Disney, Blizzard, Etc.

Just Play, LLC Freelance Digital Sculptor October 2019 - November 2019 (2 months)

Worked closely with product designers and sculptors to sculpt toys from multiple popular brands.

Hotopp Associates
Freelance 3D Modeler

October 2018 - November 2019 (1 year 2 months)

- Completed 3D models for Hotopp Clients using multiple computer software
- Organic to hard surface environment modeling with tight deadlines for theme park attractions

Education

Ringling College of Art and Design Computer Animation · (2014 - 2018)

CGTarian Animation & VFX Online School Character Modeling for Production · (2017 - 2017)

Indian River State College/Clark Advanced Learning Center Associate of Arts (A.A.), General/Art · (2011 - 2014)